#### ALOWOESIN TOLUWALASE SOLOMON

Geophysicist and Customer service Representative

Mobile: 07089327276 || Email: alowoesintoluwalase@gmail.com || Address: Ogun, Nigeria

#### **Profile:**

Dedicated Geophysicist and Customer Service Representative with a passion for delivering excellence in both scientific analysis and client interactions, coupled with a strong background in addressing customer inquiries, resolving issues, and ensuring customer satisfaction. Skilled in blending technical expertise with exceptional communication skills to provide top-notch service and build lasting relationships with clients.

**Skills:** 

- > Excellent communication skills
- Problem-solving
- ➤ Active-listening
- > Customer-centric approach
- > Strong problem-solving skills
- Leadership and team management
- > Conflict resolution
- > Project, seminar writing
- > Geophysical field work expert

# **Work Experience:**

### Ogun-Oshun River Basin Development Authority Abeokuta, Ogun-State.

National youth service corps

2023-2024

- Assisted in conducting ground water surveys and drilling of ground water for customers.
- Data collection, iteration and analysis.
- Assisted in attending to complain from customers presenting bids for federal government contracts.

### University of Ibadan, Oyo-state.

Civil engineer laboratory

June-August 2023

Internship

- Helped assist customers who came in for block testing and analysis
- Assisting in conducting tests to analyze the structural integrity of materials for customers.

# Eniade Resources int. Biz Akobo, Ibadan, Oyo-State.

Dec 2018 – August 2019

Internship

- Repairs of faulty submersible pumping machine and installation for customers
- Assisted in sales and marketing of pipes and borehole accessories to customers.
- Conducting ground water surveys and drilling of ground water for customers.

# Kenny-Moy frozen food store, Ibadan, Oyo-State.

March 2015-

June2017

Sale-rep

- Manage sales, inflow and outflows of goods
- Attending and resolving customer complain about our product

# **Educational Background:**

**BSc.** Applied Geophysics – Federal university Oye-Ekiti-State, Ekiti State.

2017-2022

#### **Personal Data:**

Date of Birth: 15<sup>th</sup> March 2000 Place of Birth Oyo State

Sex Male
Marital Status: Single
State of Origin: Osun-State

Local Govt. Area: Iwo local government

Nationality: Nigerian Religious: Christianity

Language Spoken: English and Yoruba

### Hobbie

Travelling, playing drums and Talking

Reference available on request